So, it becomes deen for you,
it becomes worship for you.
So, when you avoid rebar,
for example, in your business
transaction,
that business transaction
becomes an Ibadah for
you, for the sake of Allah.
When you avoid selling what
you don't
have, for example, you don't
own,
for example,
that your business
transaction becomes a means
of Ibadah for you.
So, this is how our worldly
affairs
becomes Ibadah for we,
the people of Islam.
When you dress, you wear
clothes,
what you wear, it fulfills
the limit,
the instructions, the
restrictions of the Sharia
are considered,
when you select the material
that you
wear, and how you wear it.
All of these have rules in
our
religion, Islam.
In fact, as simple as wearing
a
ring, which hand do you wear
the
ring?